Hello everyone, so this is our
first video here,
I'm going to talk a little about the
motivations that led me to record this
video here, right?
I had to find
material and things like that in Portuguese
when programming the apps, so the idea was to
make some tutorials, I don't know
yet how many there will be, but we'll
start from the beginning, from the installation
of the visual studio to the installation of the IDF Plugin
and it will  then following with some
implementations there that I will end up
deciding during the
execution of the
videos. So this first one we will
do then the installation of Visual
Studio and the installation of IDF in Visual
Studio
then in Visual Studio we will download it
from this website  Here is the Visual Studio that
we are going to use, we are going to
download it here, as I already downloaded it, I am just
going to install it, so
we go here, accept the terms,
I will install everything in the directories that are
standard for Visual Studio,
I always like it  to add these two
options here
they are, when you
right-click on the desktop, they
place Visual Studio in the
context menu
and here we do the installation. So
let's wait to
fix my window here,
adjust it to the  video size
So this here is the Visual
Studio interface which is where we will work,
it comes out here on a welcome screen and
from there we will come here and
start installing the plugins so
we will use
the plugins  there is a very easy installation
here so we can start working
with this one we will need some
plugins And then we will look for the
first one here which is IDF we will
look for IDF here and this first
option here so
don't install me
So, to install this
first guy here,
we will take it and start
configuring this plugin. So
we will press the F1 key here.
And then this option will appear here,
configure spdf, we will click
here, we have three options
The ideal would be for us to use something
that if we already have here, right?
So as I had already installed
another version here I could use this one
but I'm going to put Express right
here and we'll get it What version
do we want to get DF  right, I
'm going to put version 5.0 here, the
directories where it will save it, right? And here
will be the repository from where it will
download, so it will download version 5 from github,
which is a release, and it will save it
in these folders here
from there onwards.  We are now going to wait
for this guy to download all
the plugins here, here all the tools
he needs
So guys, as soon as he configures it,
he will show us this message
here and we already have it The plugin is already
practically configured,
he will probably ask us  a few more plugins
later for us to install, I already
installed the C part here, but right? It should contain
containers, which are some plugins that
IDF uses.
But let's go now,
it will show us this
welcome screen, so let's now configure
our first project here  let's
create a new project here so we
're going to press F1 and it's going to open this
little screen here we're going to type IDF there
PDF and here Type thousand it's going to
appear there, the new Project we're going to
click on this guy here
we're going to give a  name for our
project so
our project will be the first
project
pay attention here as there are some
details that can cause a lot of
problems for us to have to configure
spaces in the name of the project then here it is very
bad, so try not to leave
spaces here put the underline  Or put a
camera Case something like that
in the project in the
project there so as not to leave spaces
there
here the directory it will save or just
go to documents s32 Project
we select the development board here
So I'm going to launch this
egg kit to the port That would be where it is
connected And  this space here we use
to place a component the
components we will deal with in the video
later on there will be another
content there will be a video just dealing
with them there on how we place
these components within our
project for now we will  leave it
empty let's click on choose the
template
here it presents us with three templates
or if we want to get it from the IDF
it has several examples here it is, I'll
take it let me
take a look at this template
app here it is an empty template
I generally use it to start my  projects
But it would be very interesting if we
came here and watched hello
world, right?
Let's create from hello world
So we're going to create a new project
from hello world
just so we can demonstrate it here so
he already created this project there  he created it
in those folders there and that one is asking
me to open Visual Studio there
inside that folder So this here is
our project window so we
can see here
that there is a whole structure that
our IDF plugin there created so there is
here within the vsco point of some
configuration files
Jason so we will work
on them later for now we
will not change anything in it we will leave everything the
default configuration as it
is inside me Hello Word So this
guy he already does the  import of
some libraries from the system
and from here in the mother app it will
print a hello world and here it will
get some information from esp, right it
will print here the size of the memory
when we have it here it will
count up to 10 seconds  it will slow down
So we'll take it here, I'll
close these messages here because I don't
want to install these extensions here,
so we'll take it here, we'll
configure our Extra here, right, so
here we configure the port, right, I already
had it configured there, so it's with  three
for this project here we configure
the esc that we have so first
project it will show that the list
So mine is an s32 from this kit
here we can clean the
project if we have already seen
something  here we can do a
Clean here and it deletes that Build folder
here in this guy here he records
here we will configure the
very important recording method so ours it will
be by art we will record it
by serial with 3
here is a  monitor where we will open
a terminal and get the
esp responses that it is sending through the terminal and
here I will use this little fire which is
where it builds Flash and then
it opens the monitor which is this little screen
here so  let's click there and let's
wait
then it comes here a hello world most
showed the number of doe here the
memory size right it went there and restarted that's
what we expected here from our
code then
installed then
[Music]
visual studio along with  the plugin here is
the IDF,
right this guy here installed along with
it we can now program and
record
in this video So let's stay here,
thank you very much to everyone who watched
until the end so I thank you all and see you in
the next video thanks