Hello everyone, so today we're going to
another video, so I decided. So today,
I'm going to configure The Burger, I'm going to use the d-link together with espius,
so with that we can set the
breakbonds, stop, look at the
variables, how are they?  the state of the
variables within UESP, right, so that's
what we're going to do today, so we're going to
do this configuration and we're going to take a
project that we had already done
in the previous video
and we're going to do some testing there, so let's get
started.
So this one is the  project that we
had done so in the previous video
I enlarged it a little here since
we have this area to
work with so I'm using
a d-link
and here we have to make some
settings within Visual Studio, right,
to be able to  it identifies this
one The Burger here, right, along with Open
ocd, right, and I managed to debug the esp so
in the settings here we will get
first thing we will come here, right And we
will define here our our
flash method here as gateg
doing this I  I had commented about the
configuration files here today we
are going to change them so by doing this
in sevenths it will put this
option here right then in yours there will
be this guy here who is that kit
that we configured there when
we created the  project, so this guy
here, we're not going to use him because
we don't have this kit,
right
?  link and here we
will put our target as the s32 If you
have another computer, for example, there we will
put the target of the computer you
have, so I have the kit here,
my kit is an esp 32, I will put it
here and here  We don't need to touch
anything else so we give it a control
Burgers only
has this Launcher which is this
configuration here So we go
I'm going to deduct it here
and then here you will see that it goes
when I press control S here it
will appear that the configurations o
esp Open the CD which  this is mine here,
so within these settings
we will have the type of The Burger,
right, which is CPP, the Burger, here will
be the type of the request, here where
our build folder is, right, it will be inside
the project, here, build, where will it go?  our program will be
build
here
So this guy here will change
according to the name of your project
so within build there will be a file
there with the name of Elf with a dot Elf there
that lets me see where this guy
is here.  So this one is the first
project,
if I click on it just to select it, it's
not this guy here,
so this one will be the name of
your project, and then you'll
put
this pointing to this
workspace variable here, the build  the name of
your project, right? In my case, this is the
first project, dot Elf, which will be the
program where he will attack mi
the Burger Pet, this guy here will also
be according to
your installation, you can see
that he  it's here inside my user, right, I
know
Vick's HBR users, it would be there, right,
specific point where I did the
installation, right, the specific one
here depends on the version you're going to
use, you can see that here mine,
I have two
ready, just show them here
Oh mine I have two I have version
4 which is this one and I have version 5
as I'm using version 5 I came
to this one from below so it will go
here in this 11.2 inside this guy here
we will have the extensions  there, the Bin folder
and here we will take and look for
this file here which is an exz point
which will then be this guy here
that we will use for s32 and
from there we will have to do
a  configuration, then in the
J link file, which is this guy here,
initially he will only have this
configuration of the link adaptor, we
will put this guy's Speed ​​where
he will work and the
transport layer, so we will put
a file like this  file it is there within
the installation so this can change
according to the installation in my case
here it is within my user specific point we
go here in Tools we will look
here for opinion CD here also same
thing as I have two versions I
I have version 4.4 and version 5, I have
two installations here of their pince, they have
different versions, so as I'm
using it, let's go to this version,
opinion CD
share
Open CD script and here within the
interface we will have the d-lin that
goes  have some other interface so it's
this file here that we're going to
change, I already have it open here
inside visual studio you can see
that the address here is the same so just
close it here And this here was the other
file which is what  we
pointed it out inside the Launcher, inside this
guy from seventh
32 CFG, this one we don't need to
touch, but if anyone wants to take a
look at it, we'll come back here
inside
it's
target scripts and here we'll have the
computers that  we have then we have
another 32 C2 S3 then we can if you have a
different computer than the one I have here for
example if the person has a C2 they will
select this one
doing this then we will go to
the commands that Visual Studio will
send it to connect This guy there
so here we will say that the
target is the local domain, right on port 333
that when I start adb it will
create some ports for the bug So
we will create a server it will
we will connect  with Visual Studio
on this server, here is a watch point, right
here, monitor to give a route and
flush the Rex, we make these
settings then we will be
able to publish it, we will have to
make some changes to the Drive there
too, right?
jailink so I'll leave everything there in the
description I'll leave a link to
these files here with
and with the driver files there So
let me take a look here so
we'll use this USB Tool drivers
when you
come and put the d-link in  In
your Windows, it will have this driver here,
but this driver will not work
with adb, we will have to come here, I
came here, select, we will
select this Win USB
so it can work, so
we will come here,  little program comes
Boot it to the USB it will appear
here as in USB you can take a close up
from there it
is practically all configured Let's
do a test but if we see
our
hello world here also here we will press
F5 and we will see what  what will happen
let's see if everything will happen ok if
it will generate an error
then we had an error
It is saying that it was unable to
connect let's go why did this happen
because our Open ocd is
not running
so you saw it there  after I
clicked it, it runs, it stays here with
this little Green mark Here it says
that it's running So let's press this
five again,
it couldn't start the bug, I'll
press F5 again, let's see if
it can connect
now.  When he connects, sometimes he
can't connect to the server, which did
n't even happen to me, when he
connects this Veloso bar where it
will turn orange, then you know that The
banner is connected And we're
already starting to be able to stop within the
code  oh, so here I'm going to send it
forward, it's going to stop at this other
breakpoint that I put down there,
you can see here that we
can already identify that the i, right?
We can now see
what's inside these variables
here, we can also put them
for inspection, right?
Let me put a variable here, I
'll need the name,
put it here for the line to inspect this one, I got
the name wrong, let's delete it, let's
go
chip  info so here we can see, you can
monitor each variable, we
can see the call stack, so
what is happening in each trade
like
this, what I wanted to demonstrate
to you was this configuration, then,
of esp
on the display platform  studio of how
we configure Visual Studio to
be able to open the CD and
connect to it, right, make the open
CD connect to the esp so that we can
connect to this Open ocv show that how
it works so the variables
there  what we can see from
esp
through this the Burger
and I leave it there so thank you very much
to those who watched the video, if you like it
and share it with people, give it a like,
this helps us to spread it
to more people  so thank you very much,
thanks